Yes, on Lee Dong-jin's Pyiyakiha, we have a truly special guest with us today.
Director Lee Jung-jae is here with us.
Hello.
So, there are now only two weeks left until the release.
Yes, that's right.
If I try to imagine how it is for you as the director right now, how should I put it?
On the one hand, you must be feeling good, but on the other hand, a bit…
Like your blood is drying up.
Nervous as well—how do you feel?
How are you feeling these days?
I thought I would be really nervous at the press screening, but I actually wasn't trembling that badly.
Yes, yes.
Since they are all film people as well, I ended up thinking, "Ah, I've just done my best here."